Finding Aid for Mike Wallace papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Television and newspaper career 1956-1963
  - New York Post Column, September 1957-August 1958
    - Interviews
      - Andrews, T. Coleman (state's rights) December 19, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Arends, Leslie (defense policy) March 7, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Anslinger, Harry (narcotics) September 26-27, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Asimov, Isaac October 8, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Axelrod, George (comedy) December 4, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Azkoul, Dr. Karim (Lebanon) June 23, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Backus, Jim, unused undated (Box 4)
      - Bailey, Herbert (cancer research) August 5, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Baker, Dr. William O. (science) October 22, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Bankhead, Tallulah September 5, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Barnett, M. Robert (blind man) December 10, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Barr, Stringfellow (U.S. colleges) February 19, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Barrymore, Diana May 12, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Bartley, William W., unused March, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Beach, Samuel (unemployment) June 11, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Beaton, Cecil, unused January, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Beck, Dave (Teamsters) July 21, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Bellamy, Ralph February 18, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Belle, Earl (millionaire) April 16, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Benguettat, Adda (Algeria) April 17, 1958, May 22, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Benny, Jack, unused undated (Box 4)
      - Benton, Senator William (science education) October 24, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Berger, Dr. Herbert (narcotics), unused October, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Bergman, George (math genius) February 20, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Bernstein, Leonard, unused undated (Box 4)
      - Bigelow, Albert (nuclear disarmament) February 10, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Bitar (El-Bitar), Salah (Syria) October 29, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Blanshard, Paul, unused 1958 (Box 4)
      - Bleyer, Archie (rock 'n roll) December 18, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Bloom, Mr., unused undated (Box 4)
      - Bob and Ray June 13, 1958 (Elliot, Bob and Goulding, Ray) (Box 4)
      - Boone, Pat December 11, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Booth, John (veterans policy) July 28, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Borgnine, Ernest October 14, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Bowles, Chester, unused undated (Box 4)
      - Boyd, Rev. Malcolm (religion revival) May 26, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Bradbury, Ray February 26, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Braden, Spruille (Latin America) May 19-20, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Branden, Nathaniel (neuroses) June 27, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Brazzi, Rossano April 3, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Briscoe, Robert (Ireland) March 27, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Brockhurst, Gerald (modern art), unused undated (Box 4)
      - Brodie, Ralph (Little Rock High School student) September 8, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Browder, Earl (U.S. Communist Party) August 14, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Brown, Mrs. W. B. (school desegregation) February 24, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Buckley, William Jr. undated (Box 4)
      - Burney, Surgeon-General Leroy (Asian flu) September 4, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Burns, Sheelagh (mixed marriages) October 30, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Burrows, Abe (psychoanalysis) December 20, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Buttons, Red, unused May, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Cafritz, Gwen (western civilization) February 27, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Cage, John (communism and art) June 10, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Caldwell, Erskine November 22, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Call Girl November 18, 1957 (Box 4)
      - Cantor, Eddie, unused undated (Box 4)
      - Carere, Christine July 15, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Celler, Representative Emanuel (alcohol on TV) August 13, 1958 (Box 4)
      - Chamales, Tom (Chinese war crimes) January 2, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Chandler, Digby (Alaska flag) July 2, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Channing, Carol, unused January, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Chaplin, Charlie Jr. July 29, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Chennault, C. L. (Red China) November 1, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Cherne, Leo (Hungary) November 6, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Churchill, Randolph February 25, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Civil War, unused undated (Box 5)
      - Clement, Governor Frank (desegregation) October 4, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Cleveland, Harlan, unused undated (Box 5)
      - Cliburn, Van, unused May, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Collins, Cyrus, unused (Box 5)
      - Commager, Henry Steele (teachers) January 8, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Confidential and Hollywood, unused, undated (Box 5)
      - Cott, Ted (TV censorship) June 9, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Cournand, Edouard (perfume) January 16, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Crandall, Lee (zookeeper), unused June 24, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Crawford, Joan November 12, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Crosby, Bob August 7, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Curtis, Tony October 28, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Dalrymple, Jean (art) May 23, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Daniels, Jonathan July 8, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Dauphin, Charles (de Gaulle) May 28, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Davis, Sammy Jr., unused undated (Box 5)
      - Davis, Colonel William O. June 12, 1958 (Box 5)
      - DeBilio, Dr. Francis (teen violence) February 6-7, 1958 (Box 5)
      - de Havilland, Olivia July 7, 1958 (Box 5)
      - de Regis, Irene March 24, 1958 (Box 5)
      - de Seversky, Major Alexander September 20, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Deiss, Jay, unused undated (Box 5)
      - Deren, Maya (filmmaker) April 4, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Dichter, Dr. Ernest (U.S. image) November 19, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Dooley, Thomas March 10, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Douglas, Kirk November 20, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Douglas, Senator Paul (economic depression) March 3, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Dryer, Dr. Bernard, unused July, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Duke, Angier Biddle (political refugees) November 27, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Dunning, John (science) October 23, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Eastman, Max, unused (Box 5)
      - Eaton, Cyrus (McCarthyism) June 3, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Eckberg, Anita April 21, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Eisendrath, Rabbi Maurice, unused June, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Eisenhower, Edgar, unused undated (Box 5)
      - Eisenhower, Milton, unused September, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Ewing, Oscar (health policy) August 27, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Erickson, Eric (espionage) June 30, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Fahmy, Hussein (Arab-Israeli conflict) April 24, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Faiz, Ahmad (Pakistan) March 31, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Farley, James A., unused September, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Farrell, James, unused December, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Fast, Howard, unused September, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Faubus, Governor Orval November 8, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Field, Herman (prisoner in Poland) February 4-5, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Finkletter, Thomas (science) October 21, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Fischer, Dr. Irving (abortion) March 18, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Ford, Eileen (fashion) April 8, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Ford, Paul (old age) November 4, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Forster, Arnold D. (anti-Semitism) April 15, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Frankel, Stan, unused undated (Box 5)
      - Franklyn, Dr. Robert (breast implants) (Box 5)
      - Frazier, E. Franklin March 19-20, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Fuller, Edmund (literary critic) July 24, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Gable, Clark, unused September, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Gabor, Zsa Zsa September 16, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Galbraith, Dr. John K. September 23, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Galbraith, Dr. John K., unused undated (Box 5)
      - Garroway, Dave May 7, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Gavin, Catherine (Britain and U.S.) May 8, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Gazzara, Ben April 18, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Gelb, Lawrence (bleaching hair), unused June 10, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Geraud, Andre, unused undated (Box 5)
      - Gillespie, Dizzy October 11, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Gingold, Hermione May 16, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Ginzburg, Ralph (erotic literature) July 10, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Gode, Alexander December 12, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Goldfine, Mrs. Bernard (fame) July 3, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Goodman, Dody January 27, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Gorman, Mike (mental illness) February 14, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Graham, Rev. Billy, unused August, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Granger, Chef Clement October 10, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Greenwald, Dr. Harold (prostitution) April 15, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Hackett, Buddy and Murray, Jan June 19, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Handwerg, John (golfing) May 2, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Harrison, Robert (libel suits) December 3, 1957 (Box 5)
      - Hartman, Don (censorship) February 13, 1958 (Box 5)
      - Hathaway, Gordon (mood medicine) May 27, 1958 (see also Nye, Louis) (Box 5)
      - Hayakawa, Sessue March 28, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Heikal, Mohammed (U.S. press and Arabs) April 23, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Hope, Bob, unused September, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Horne, Lena March 6, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Hunter, Evan (suburban life) June 18, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Hussein, King, unused 1957 (Box 6)
      - Inge, William (theatre critic) August 28, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Javits, Jacob February 12, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Jawad, Ambassador Hashim (Iraq) July 22, 1958 (Box 6)
      - John, Mr. (fashion) December 2, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Johnson, David (composer) May 6, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Kazan, Elia September 13, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Keating, William (organized crime) July 9, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Keating, William (labor) November 13-14, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Kefauver, Senator Estes September 17, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Kent, Rockwell (right to travel) January 9, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Kerouac, Jack January 21, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Kerr, Deborah November 25, 1957 (Box 6)
      - King, Alan August 1, 1958 (Box 6)
      - King, Dr. Martin Luther Jr. July 11, 1958 (Box 6)
      - King-Hall, Comm. Sir Stephen (H-Bomb) April 29, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Kline, Dr. Nathan ('superman' drug) November 21, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Laine, Frankie September 24, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Lall, Arthur (India) August 6, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Lamantia, Philip and Kerouac, Jack (beat generation) January 22, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Lamont, Corliss September 1957 (Box 6)
      - Landau, Nina (co-ed in China) October 31, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Lansner, Kermit (education) July 31, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Lee, Gypsy Rose September 3, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Levenson, Sam (teachers) September 9, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Levin, Meyer January 17, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Lewis, Joe E. October 9, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Ley, Willie (moon mission) October 7, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Lindsay, John August 8, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Lollobrigida, Gina February 11, 1958 (Box 6)
      - London, George (culture war) January 28, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Loren, Sophia August 19, 1958 (Box 6)
      - McCarthy, Glenn, unused (Box 6)
      - McCarthy, Shane (youth fitness) October 15, 1957 (Box 6)
      - McClellan, Senator John (organized crime) September 10, 1957 (Box 6)
      - McCrary, Tex (America's image) August 18, 1958 (Box 6)
      - McDowall, Roddy January 31, 1958 (Box 6)
      - McKenna, Siobhan (Ireland) March 17, 1958 (Box 6)
      - MacNamara, Donal (private investigator) March 5, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Magloire, Paul (Haiti) August 15, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Mailer, Norman July 25, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Mansfield, Jayne September 11, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Marceau, Marcel April 25, 1958 (Box 6)
      - March, Hal (quiz show host) January 6, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Marshall, Thurgood September 30, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Maleter, Mrs. Pal (Hungary) June 24, 1958 (Box 6)
      - May, Elaine and Nichols, Mike April 1, 1958 (Box 6)
      - May, Dr. Jacque (psychiatry) August 4, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Mayer, Martin (advertising) April 2, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Menshikov, Ambassador Mikhail March 12-14, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Merrick, David August 29, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Merriwether, Lee (Miss America) December 24, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Mickelson, Sig (CBS news) August 21, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Murray, Jan (TV) January 30, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Myers, Rev. C. Kilmer July 30, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Nash, Ogden November 15, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Noble, John (U.S. slaves in USSR) July 1, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Nutting, Anthony (de Gaulle) May 21, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Nye, Louis May 27, 1958 (see also Hathaway, Gordon) (Box 6)
      - O'Brian, Hugh undated (Box 6)
      - O'Brien, Cathy (debutante) January 29, 1958 (Box 6)
      - O'Brien, Margaret August 11, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Ogburn, Charlton (Middle East) December 13, 1957 (Box 6)
      - O'Mahoney, Senator Joseph (prolonged illness and the Presidency) February 17, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Packard, Vance (subliminal advertising) September 6, 1957 (Box 6)
      - Pastore, Senator John (atomic energy) April 9, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Pearson, Drew June 20, 1958 (Box 6)
      - Pei, Mario (universal language) undated (Box 7)
      - Pike, Dean (James A.) (religion and commercialism) September 12, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Pogo March 21, 1958 (Kelly, Walt) (Box 7)
      - Poitier, Sidney August 26, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Porter, Representative Charles March 25, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Preminger, Otto August 22, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Queen, Ellery April 28, 1958 (Dannay, Frederic and Lee, Manfred B.) (Box 7)
      - Rand, Lester (teenage problem) December 23, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Ray, Dr. Randolph (divorce) December 17, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Ragen, Warden (Joseph) (penal system) February 21, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Reiner, Carl March 26, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Ritchard, Cyril October 3, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Robinson, Gladys (art collector) June 2, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Robinson, Jackie October 16, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Robinson, Jackie February 3, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Robinson, Sugar Ray September 18, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson June 16-17, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Rosenfield, Big Joe (radio talk show) August 25, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Rothenberg, Charles (marriage) May 5, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Russell, Bertrand February 28, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Salant, Richard (CBS news) June 26, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Sands, Tommy April 10, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Sangharakshita (Buddhist monk) undated (Box 7)
      - Sayegh, Fayez (Arab-Israel conflict) October 2, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Sayen, Clarence (jet travel) July 23, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Sayres, Paul (U.S. diplomacy) April 14, 1958 (see also Belle, Earl) (Box 7)
      - Schary, Dore December 16, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Schindler, Dr. John (sex roles) October 17, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Seberg, Jean November 26, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Schultz, Gladys Denny (obstetrics) May 14, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Simpson, Rev. Richard (political parties) May 1, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Skinner, Cornelia Otis July 16, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Smathers, Senator George (railroads) April 30, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Smith, Betty (Brooklyn) March 11, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Spiegel, Sam (movie propaganda) December 26, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Spindel, Bernard (birth control) July 18, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Stone, Dr. Abraham April 11, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Sutton, Horace, (American tourists) July 14, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Tucker, Sophie (motherhood) May 9, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Tyndall, Professor, ('eggheadism') January 24, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Umeki, Myoshi June 6, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Urrutia, Dr. Manuel April 7, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Ustinov, Peter December 5, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Van Vooren, Monique October 1, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Walter, Representative Frances (right to travel) June 4, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Warburg, James (arms race) January 3, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Waterman, Alan (science) October 25, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Watson, Dr. Goodwin (education) January 7, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Weegee (photographer) March 4, 1958 (Fellig, Arthur) (Box 7)
      - Welk, Lawrence August 20, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Wells, Hazel (alcohol and WCTU) December 31, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Wilder, Billy January 23, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Williams, Tennessee December 30, 1957 (see also Night Beat, March 28, 1957) (Box 7)
      - Wilson, Charles E. November 11, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Wilson, Sloan June 5, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Wright, Benjamin (higher education) December 6, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Wright, Loyd (civil liberties) November 7, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Wylie, Philip (TV) September 25, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Zukerman, Jacob (husband desertion) August 12, 1958 (Box 7)
  - Newsmaker Productions
    - Case History 1956 (Box 7)
      (promotional material for proposed program)
    - Perspective 1957 (Box 7)
      (budget and outline for proposed program)
    - Page One 1958 (Box 7)
      (research material and outline for proposed program)
    - Medical Detective 1959 (Box 7)
      (memo on proposed program)
    - Obligation to Tomorrow (Box 7)
      (notebook contains script and research material for proposed documentary on Albert Schweitzer)
  - Mike Wallace Interview, ABC
    - Miscellaneous (includes guest list, telegrams, and correspondence) (Box 7)
    - Press Clippings (Box 7)
    - Mickey Cohen Affair
      - Clippings (Box 7)
      - Litigation (Box 7)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 7)
    - Interviews
      - Allen, Steve July 7, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Arcaro, Eddie September 8, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Barrymore, Diana July 14, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Bridges, Harry August 18, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Browder, Earl June 2, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Buck, Pearl February 8, 1958 (Box 7)
      - Cerf, Bennett November 30, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Dali, Salvador April 21, 1958 (Box 7)
      - de Seversky, Major Alexander December 28, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Dors, Diana November 9, 1957 (Box 7)
      - Eban, Abba April 12, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Edwards, Eldon May 5, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Jessel, Georgie September 14, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Kelly, Charles (commando) June 30, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Lapp, Ralph June 9, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Lewis, Fulton Jr. February 1, 1958 (Box 8)
      - McBride, Mary Margaret June 16, 1957 (Box 8)
      - McCarthy, Glenn July 21, 1957 (Box 8)
      - McCormack, Patty, unused August 18, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Morse, Senator Wayne May 26, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Nasser, Gamal Abdel, unused April, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Nobel Prize Dinner January 11, 1958 (Box 8)
        (guests are L. Pearson, J. B. Orr, P. Buck, L. Pauling, and C. Pickett)
      - Pearson, Drew December 7, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Perkins, Tony March 22, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Roosevelt, Eleanor November 23, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Roth, Lillian April 5, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Saint, Eva Marie, unused undated (Box 8)
      - St. Cyr, Lilli October 5, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Sanger, Margaret September 21, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Seberg, Jean January 4, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Swanson, Gloria April 28, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Ustinov, Peter March 29, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Weeks, Edward August 24, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Wylie, Philip May 12, 1957 (Box 8)
      - Year-End Show 1957 (Box 8)
  - Survival and Freedom April-September 1958
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
    - Interviews
      - Adler, Mortimer September 7, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Ashmore, Harry June 29, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Dabbs, James McBride August 31, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Douglas, Justice William O. May 11, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Eaton, Cyrus May 4, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Fromm, Dr. Erich May 25, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Hutchins, Dr. Robert July 20, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Huxley, Aldous May 18, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Kissinger, Henry July 13, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Lally, Monsignor Francis June 22, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Larson, Arthur September 14, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Lodge, Henry Cabot June 15, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Niebuhr, Reinhold April 27, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Percy, Charles July 6, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Stevenson, Adlai June 1, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Weaver, Sylvester "Pat" June 8, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Weeks, Edward August 24, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Wriston, Henry August 17, 1958 (Box 8)
  - Ben Hecht Show September 1958-January 1959
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
      (includes chronological list of program topic, scripts for commercials, and correspondence)
    - Interview Guest or Topic
      - Acting, method October 10, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Actress, aspiring October 20, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Adler, Stella November 14, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Akers, Anthony November 3, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Allen, Steve November 18, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Antheil, George October 31, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Axelrod, George January 12, 1959 (Box 8)
      - Bean, Orson December 29, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Benton, Senator William October 21, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Bergaust, Ben and Haley, Andrew November 20, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Bergson, Peter October 23, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Berman, Emile Zola September 16, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Books November 11, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Briscoe, Robert November 17, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Burrows, Abe November 21, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Calitri, Charles December 16, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Capp, Al November 28, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Carroll, Luke September 23, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Cassini, Igor January 26, 1959 (Box 8)
      - Christmas Show December 25, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Ciardi, John September 26, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Dali, Salvador January 30, 1959 (Box 8)
      - Durante, Jimmy January 19-20, 1959 (Box 8)
      - Emery, Stephen December 19, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Ferrer, Jose December 5, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Foreman, Bob September 15, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Gabor, Zsa Zsa January 9, 1959 (Box 8)
      - Gingold, Hermione December 2, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Graham, Sheilah November 24, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Havoc, June January 8, 1959 (Box 8)
      - James, Charles January 27, 1959 (Box 8)
      - Journalism students October 6, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Kerouac, Jack October 17, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Keyes, Donald January 5, 1959 (Box 8)
      - King, Alexander January 16, 1959 (Box 8)
      - King, Alexander January 29, 1959 (Box 8)
      - Kitt, Eartha January 15, 1959 (Box 8)
      - Kross, Anna December 11, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Lederer, Charles October 4, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Lilo October 30, 1958 (Box 8)
      - MacNamara, Donal September 18, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Mailer, Norman, unused November, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Makarios, Archbishop November 24, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Maney, Dick September 29, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Memory Lane October 3, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Meredith, Burgess December 1, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Metalious, Grace, October 28, 1958 Television and newspaper career 1956-1963 (cont.) (Box 8)
      - Miller, Rev. William Lee September 25, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Modern Art October, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Morgan, Henry November 13, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Murtagh, John December 23, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Obituary for nobody November 7, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Page, Geraldine October 16, 1958 (Box 8)
      - Parker, Dorothy January 23, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Pegler, Westbrook October 9, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Perlman, S.J. November 6, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Preminger, Otto December 26, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Press Agents undated (Box 9)
      - Quill, Mike December 4, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Reisel, Victor January 6, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Resko, John December 9, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Robinson, Sugar Ray January 22, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Rockets (Bergaust and Haley) November 20, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Roosevelt, Teddy October 27, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Rose, Billy October 7, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Salisbury, Harrison November 25, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Schulberg, Budd December 12, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Smith and Dale December 18, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Steirman, Hy September 22, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Storm, Tempest January 2, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Swanson, Gloria October 1, 1958 (Box 9)
      - "Three on a Cloud'' January 14, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Thuri (or Thury), Rev. Helen October 24, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Todd, Mike Jr. November 10, 1958 (see also, Thuri, Helen) (Box 9)
      - United Nations October 3, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Van Vooren, Monique December 15, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Wallace, Mike November 27, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Wauger, Walter November 12, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Watts, Richard September 19, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Weegee October 2, 1958 (Box 9)
      - Wells, Hazel January 1, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Wynn, Keenan January 13, 1959 (Box 9)
      - Zeckendorf, Bill September 30, 1958 (Box 9)
      - No Guest November 3, 1958 (Box 9)
      - No Guest December 30, 1958 (Box 9)
  - WNTA Mike Wallace Interview February 1959-March 1961
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9)